H. K. NIMNAKA YASITH RAVISHAN KUMARADASA

5A, Polkotuwa Road, Rawathawatte, Moratuwa, Western Province, Sri Lanka • +94 77 0527 520 • nimnakakumaradasa1@gmail.com www.nimnakakumaradasa.com

SUMMARY

As a Computer Science graduate specializing in Software Engineering and UI/UX design, I aim to contribute significantly to any organization. My goal is to excel by combining technical skills with user-centered design, continuously improving as a professional. I strive to be a distinguished leader, fostering innovation and creating exceptional digital experiences.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Designer | Frontend Developer, Nekfa Australia PVT LTD, Colombo 02 Nov 2023 - Present

- · Assist in the development of websites for clients using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, and WordPress.
- Moderate and develop dynamic digital content for interactive screens deployed at various locations.
- Collaborate with stakeholders to gather requirements and implement solutions that meet client needs effectively.
- Ensure websites are responsive and optimized for various devices for optimal performance.
- Developed the UK project <u>Cerinca</u> site.
- To view the official websites of the Negombo Municipal Council (Sri Lanka), the Kalutara Municipal Council (Sri Lanka) and the Attanagalla Pradeshiya Sabha (Sri Lanka).

Information Security Intern, Hemas Holdings PLC, Colombo 02

Apr 2023 - Nov 2023

- · Assisted in the monitoring of Security Information and Event Management (SIEM) scenarios and notified them relevant SBUs'/parties and recommended actions to address potential security incidents.
- Proficiently utilized ManageEngine within a ServiceDesk Plus framework to manage ticket requests and inquiries. Ensured prompt issue resolution and provided exemptional support for end-users.
- Conducted a comprehensive evaluation and comparison of various Web Application Firewalls (WAF) along with their distributor and suppliers.
- · Applied design skills to create infographics and posters for company related events and innovative security awareness campaigns.
- Developed a Python script to convert .txt files to .log format, enhancing data processing and automation capabilities.

Data Entry Analyst, Horizon College, Malabe, Colombo

Oct 2020 - Nov 2020

- Entered employee salary data and student details to the SAP system.
- Helped SAP team in finalizing data documents.

SOCIAL













EDUCATION

Bachelors of Computer Science Major in Software Engineering

Jan 2020 - Feb 2024

Edith Cowan University, Colombo, Sri Lanka

• Successfully completed the Bachelor's in Computer Science degree at Edith Cowan University.

Diploma in Software Engineering

Aug 2020 - Nov 2021

Australian College of Business & Technology

• Successfully completed the Diploma Level of Computer Science.

Diploma in Adobe Photoshop

2015

New Sense Education Centre, Moratuwa, Sri Lanka

• Successfully completed the Diploma Level of Computer Science.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Technical Skills: Project Management, MS Office, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe After Effects, Figma, CorelDraw, HTML/CSS/JavaScript, React
- Soft Skills: Communication, Teamwork, Problem-Solving, Time Management
- · Languages: English, Sinhala
- Interests: Drawing, Singing, Cooking, Product Design, Dancing, Video Editing, Acting
- Certifications: Figma for UX Design, Web Development, More on LinkedIn

VOLUNTEER WORKS

Assistant Treasurer & Media Head: Students' Activity Council of ACBT
 Mar 2021 - Jan 2023

• Event Organizer & Design: Pearl Protectors

Apr 2021 - Dec 2023

• Media Unit: Young Zoologist Association of National Zoological Gardens

Dec 2019

NON-RELATED REFREES

- Mrs. Niresha Udayaratne | Assistant General Manager | Admin & HR agm@nekfa.com | (+94) 71 754 4364 | Nekfa Australia Pvt Ltd.
- Mr. Niroshan Tharanga | Cyber Security Manager | Information Security niroshan.groupit@hemas.com | (+94) 71 110 7717 | Hemas Holdings PLC
- Mr. Rukshi Rushan | Manager | Business Intelligence & Analytics <u>rukshi.groupit@hemas.com</u> | (+94) 76 227 3634 | Hemas Holdings PLC